{"Parameter Count of Method":[{"Type":"JsonConverter`1","Location":"T ReadJson(Newtonsoft.Json.JsonReader, System.Type, T, Boolean, Newtonsoft.Json.JsonSerializer)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 5.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"AsyncUtils","Location":"System.Threading.Tasks.Task WriteAsync(System.IO.TextWriter, Char[], Int32, Int32, System.Threading.CancellationToken)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 5.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"AsyncUtils","Location":"System.Threading.Tasks.Task`1[System.Int32] ReadAsync(System.IO.TextReader, Char[], Int32, Int32, System.Threading.CancellationToken)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 5.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"JavaScriptUtils","Location":"Void WriteEscapedJavaScriptString(System.IO.TextWriter, System.String, Char, Boolean, Boolean[], Newtonsoft.Json.StringEscapeHandling, Newtonsoft.Json.IArrayPool`1[System.Char], Char[] ByRef)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 8.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"JavaScriptUtils","Location":"System.Threading.Tasks.Task WriteEscapedJavaScriptStringAsync(System.IO.TextWriter, System.String, Char, Boolean, Boolean[], Newtonsoft.Json.StringEscapeHandling, Newtonsoft.Json.JsonTextWriter, Char[], System.Threading.CancellationToken)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 9.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"StringUtils","Location":"System.String FormatWith(System.String, System.IFormatProvider, System.Object, System.Object, System.Object)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 5.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"StringUtils","Location":"System.String FormatWith(System.String, System.IFormatProvider, System.Object, System.Object, System.Object, System.Object)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 6.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"SerializationErrorCallback","Location":"System.IAsyncResult BeginInvoke(System.Object, System.Runtime.Serialization.StreamingContext, Newtonsoft.Json.Serialization.ErrorContext, System.AsyncCallback, System.Object)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 5.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"ExtensionDataSetter","Location":"System.IAsyncResult BeginInvoke(System.Object, System.String, System.Object, System.AsyncCallback, System.Object)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 5.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."},{"Type":"JsonSerializerInternalReader","Location":"System.Object CreateNewObject(Newtonsoft.Json.JsonReader, Newtonsoft.Json.Serialization.JsonObjectContract, Newtonsoft.Json.Serialization.JsonProperty, Newtonsoft.Json.Serialization.JsonProperty, System.String, Boolean ByRef)","Problem":"Method has more than 4 parameters. Has 6.","Criteria":"Parameter Count of Method","Significance":0,"Solution":"Reduce number of parameters or provide overload with less parameters."}]}